DENIS BUTSKY

{FRONT END DEVELOPER}

CONTACT

Vancouver, BC +17788368978 developer@denisbutsky.com linkedin.com/in/denisbutsky github.com/nthbutsky denisbutsky.com

ABOUT

A curious Swiss Army knife front end developer with a strong eye for good design and a keen understanding of each tool's purpose with total combined experience of two years in development who is looking for a place to broaden enthusiasm around IT industry, deepen knowledge in every possible way regarding web, mobile and beyond. There is no impossible task out there that can't be solved, some of them need more specific knowledge which is simply a matter of time and pixel peeping.

SKILLS

JavaScript, TypeScript, Vue.JS, Nuxt.JS, Node.JS, SCSS, Tailwind, REST API, Firebase, Git, Bootstrap, Alpine.js, Docker, Webpack, English, French, Polish, Italian, Ukrainian, Russian, fast learning, accountability, problem solving, critical and analytical thinking, time management, flexibility, stress resistance.

EXPERIENCE

Front End Developer | Convidera | Germany/Ukraine | Jan 2022 - present Intensively worked on successful and profitable projects (REMEX.de, Virtrex.de, Speekly.de) using diverse modern tools in the industry (Vue.JS, Nuxt.JS, Tailwind, Alpine.JS, Autho, GraphQL, Livewire, Laravel, Nova) in teams of various sizes. Also when russian invasion started I volunteered to IT army of Ukraine project.

Web Developer | Entrepreneur | Ukraine | Feb 2021 - Jan 2022 Successfully developed and delivered commercial Web project on JS. Created several pet projects based on different Stacks and made dozens of landings. Worked hard on gaining expertise in mentioned competencies.

Support Engineer / Fleet Manager | CloudMade | Ukraine | Feb 2020 - Feb 2021 Positively dealt with Android and Unix based device testing, setup, customization and troubleshooting. Researched market and proposed hardware upgrade for the projects continuity. Efficiently implemented remote fleet management during COVID-19 in 6 countries.

EDUCATION

Harvard University | CS50x | Mar - Dec 2021 Beetroot Academy | Front-End Development | Jul - Nov 2021 Scrum.org | Scrum Muster I | May 2020 National University | Romance-Germanic Philology | 2007 - 2011 European University | Information Systems | 2006 - 2007

INTERESTS

Photography, cinematography, DYI, 3d printing, handcrafting, gear, tech, arduino, linguistics, travelling, all sorts of vehicles.